

Sydney

0412 269 477 601, 303 Pitt Street, Sydney NSW 2000

Melbourne

+61 3 9939 4134 204, 546 Collins Street, Melbourne VIC 3000

Xiaohan Li (Jacky)

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I recently graduated from the University of Sydney with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Technology. I am mainly skilled with project management with different methodologies and back-end development, but I am also familiar with HTML and JavaScript. In addition to studying, I also have successive internship experiences during the holidays. I worked as an Assistant analyst in Shanghai Ouyi Market Consulting company. I was in charge of the scheduling, data processing, customer, and partner communication. I am very willing to face and solve the problem with responsibility and team spirit. I am also good in empathy so that I can improve the product from the customer's point of view. What's more, I have experienced a whole web platform development project with both front-end and backend which establish in the AWS could server. I desire to learn and grow as a product manager/ data analyst / front-end developer.

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

training

Aug 2017 – Dec 2020 University of Sydney

Sydney Bachelor of Computer Science and Technology

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov 2016 – May 2017, Shanghai Ouyi Market Consulting Co., Ltd., China
Nov 2018 – Feb 2019,
Dec 2019 – Feb 2020
Shanghai the Executive Department of the Ministry

Assistant analyst(Intern)
Scheduled time of other partner companies in various regions to take part in an interview

- Invited and Scheduled medical product-related personnel (doctors, nurses, patients) and qualitative interview with the interviewee experience
- Evaluated and feedbacked questionnaire accuracy
- Processed and analyzed simple data
- Completed three projects independently and supported twelve projects of the execution phase

PROJECT EXPERIENCE / VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE / OTHER ACTIVITIES

Sep 2017 – Nov 2017 "Happy Seeker" Website Sydney Team leader

- Designed and implemented a static website based on the concept of 'Seeking Happiness' using HTML and CSS as a team leader with a group of six
- Using Waterfall as project management methodology since it is a small project.
- I was responsible for the requirement analysis, communication between the client and the team, and among team members, and product presentation
- I designed the website concept and logic, using recommendations for the students' four basic needs, clothing, food, housing, and transportation near the university of Sydney to respond the theme
- I designed and coded part of UI, the 'food recommendation' page

Sydney

Melbourne



Mar 2019 - June 2019 Sydney 0412 269 477 601, 303 Pitt Street, +61 3 9939 4134 204, 546 Collins Street,

Project Management Plan for (Colesworth" to Implement Aftermony Team member

- Produced a management plan and two presentations through scope, risk, schedule, budget, communication, and stakeholder management with the Agile approach aim to 'Make Life Easier' as a team member with a group of six
- Using Agile as project management methodology since the project is a management plan which needs regular communication between the client and the team
- I was responsible for meeting minutes and time schedule of meetings of the group
- I put forward a lot of opinions on customer's requirements and risk migration
- The report and product presentation were completed by the whole team

Oct 2019 – Nov 2019 Classification Sydney Researcher

- Implemented the K-NN and Naïve Bayes algorithms in Python with other classifiers in 'Weka' to test performance with the same data set by machine learning and reported it
- I designed and coded my own K-NN and Naïve Bayes algorithms
- I used 10-fold stratified cross-validation to generate the training data
- I reported the results and patterns between same algorithms of mine and Weka's, and between different classifiers after training with different training data in the same data set

Apr 2020 – May 2020 E Vending machine Sydney Scrum Master

- Implemented a vending machine software with basic UI, functionalities and several different authorities using JAVA combined with Jira, GitHub, Gradle and Jenkins as a Scrum Master with a group of five
- Using Scrum as project management methodology since the client wants periodic, 2 weeks as a period, feedback on progress
- I assisted the product manager with the requirement analysis using user story, formulation of the Scrum goals and backlogs, and software logic using ERD.
- I was responsible for the sprint planning, daily scrum, sprint review and management on Jira.
- I designed the command lined UI and functions of 'Cashier', 'Pay by Card' and 'Owner' parts of the vending machine.
- The reports and product presentations in total of 3 sprints were completed by the whole team.

Aug 2020 – Dec 2020 Web Platform for Client-Supplier Business Management Sydney Product manager

- Implemented a home-service B2C web platform on the supplier side including both front-end using VUE Framework and back-end using Django Framework as a product manager with a group of seven
- Using Agile as project management methodology as client's requirement
- I was responsible for the communication between the client and the team, between our team and another team who is responsible for the customer side, and among team members
- I was responsible for the scope, requirement analysis, formulation of schedule and main UI design along with the product manager from another group
- I designed the low-fidelity prototype 'sign in/log in' and 'enquire' using balsamiq
- I designed and established the database using MySQL in Django framework
- I designed and coded the password protection function by adding salt to hashing
- We completed the docking work with the front end used restful API to send Json object and build the website on AWS server
- The report and product presentation were completed by the whole team



Sydney

0412 269 477 601, 303 Pitt Street, Sydney NSW 2000 Melbourne

+61 3 9939 4134 204, 546 Collins Street, Melbourne VIC 3000

Jun 2020 – Aug 2020

Owlee Health Store

Sydney

Ctott

- Receiving and serving customers
- Count and ration the goods
- Recommend and sell goods
- Pack and send goods
- Reconciliation of goods

SKILLS

- IT Skills:
 - o Computer Language: C, Java, Python, html, JavaScript, SQL
 - o Statistic Software: R Studio, MATLAB, Magma
 - o Office Software: Word, Excel, PowerPoint
 - Other software: Jira, GitHub, Jenkins, Docker, Gradle, Weka
 - System Modeling: Object Relationship Diagram, Use Case Modeling, ERD, DFD, Gantt Chart, WBS
 - o Project Management Methodology: Agile, Scrum, Kanban, XP, Waterfall
- Language Skills: Fluent in English/Mandarin
- Soft Skills:
 - Responsible to the team and project
 - Team spirit
 - Strong communication skills
 - Good in empathy
 - Good in logical thinking and critical thinking

Email: info@ecarecareers.com.au

Website: www.ecarecareers.com.au